And now let's just go back and change. Hey, what's good.
现在，让我们回来修改一下这句 "Hey whats good?"
We'll refresh our front end. And now we can see you've done it,
刷新一下前端，现在我们可以看到，已经完成了
we've created a minimalistic website
我们已经创建好了一个简化的网站
that allows us to connect to the blockchain and call functions from a front end. And from a website,
它使我们能够从前端网站连接到区块链上并调用函数
this is absolutely massive,
这绝对是一个巨大的成就
you should be incredibly proud and incredibly excited with yourself.
你应当为自己感到无比的骄傲和自豪
Now, this is definitely a minimalistic version.
但这肯定只是一个非常简化的版本
And we're going to work with more powerful and more modern front end frameworks.
我们之后会使用更加强大，更加现代化的前端框架
But this will give you an idea of exactly what's going on
但这能让你了解到，在我们使用更高级的前端时
behind the scenes when we're working with those more advanced front ends,
它们的背后到底发生了些什么
and we'll style them up. So they look a little bit better than this.
不过我们会进行一些样式设计，让它们看起来会比现在更加好看
But with that being said, you've just learned the basics of how these front ends work.
不管怎么样，你刚刚已经学会了这些前端工作的基础知识
And now that you know how to push things up to get,
之前你已经了解过如何把它们推送到 git 上了
I highly recommend you start pushing all of these projects up to your GitHub,
我强烈推荐你把这些项目都推送到 GitHub 上
they will be a record that you've actually done the work
它们会成为一种记录，以表明你确实已经完成了这些工作
and you've built these smart contracts.
以及你已经构建过这些智能合约了
And if you're looking to get an internship down the line,
如果你正在寻找实习的机会
if you're looking to help other GitHub projects,
如果你想为其它 GitHub 项目提供帮助
this will be a record of hey, I can do this,
这都将成为一种记录，就像在说，嘿，我能做到
what I can build look at what I know how to do
看看我构建了些什么，我知道该怎么做
so congratulations on your first full stack or your first front end application.
祝贺你完成了你的第一个前端应用，第一份全栈工作
Before we move on, let's do a quick refresher of everything we've learned here.
在我们继续之前，让我们快速地回顾一下这一节中学习到的所有内容
So number one, typically,
第一点是，通常情况下
you want the repository or your code base. For your back end for your smart contracts to be a different repository than your front end,
你要将你的后端智能合约仓库或者说代码库，与前端分离
your front end code is going to be a combination of HTML and JavaScript.
你的前端代码是 HTML 和 JavaScript 的组合
When we have a wallet like meta mask,
当我们有一个类似 MetaMask 这样的钱包时
we're injecting these browser based wallets into the window object of our browsers
我们会将这些基于浏览器的钱包注入到浏览器的 "window" 对象里
like window dot Aetherium.
比如说 "window.ethereum"
Each browser will have a different extension here,
不同的浏览器会有不同的扩展名
reason we do this,
我们这样做的原因是
we want to connect to the RPC URL that's built into our meta masks.
我们想连接到内置在 MetaMask 中的 "RPC URL"
And in this way, we're making the same API calls to an RPC URL
在这种方式下，我们对 "RPC URL" 进行的 API 调用
as we do in hard hat as we do in remix as we do in ethers, etc,
就和我们在 Hardhat, Remix, ethers 等工具中所做的完全一样
we created our first promise based function
我们创建了我们的第一个基于 "Promise" 的函数
where we had a listener kickoff, and we wrapped it in a promise to say,
在这个函数中，我们有一个监听器启动器，并且把它包装进了一个 "Promise" 中，而且告诉它
hey, we want to wait for our listener to finish
嘿，我们要等待监听器完成监听
since this is a promise based function,
由于这是一个基于 "Promise" 的函数
we set a weight listen for transaction mind and we waited for this transaction to finish
所以我们写的是 `await listenForTransactionMine` 并等待交易完成
so that on our front end, once our transaction finished going through,
这样在我们的前端中，一旦我们的交易完成
we can tell the user it's finished going through
我们就可以告诉用户它已经完成了
and we can continue doing other stuff.
这样我们就可以继续干其它事了
Give yourself that round of applause and let's move on to the next section.
给自己鼓个掌吧，然后让我们进入到下一节中